trade-24.com 2015-12-11

# Privacy Policy | Trade 24

No matter if you are a former or an existing client or just a visitor on our website, your privacy is one of Trade24 Investments Ltd. Group which is registered at Trident Chambers, PO Box 1388, Victoria, Mahe, Seychelles (the " **Company** ") main concerns. Therefore, the Company is committed to safeguard all personal information.

By providing the Company with your personal information such as Full Name, Mailing Address, ID number, Passport Number etc., you are providing the Company with full consent to gather, utilize, store and protect the information provided in the manner described below.

 _When is Information Collected from Company's Clients:_

  * When opening a Live/Demo trading account with Company.
  * When funding your personal trading account.
  * When withdrawing from your personal trading account.

 _The Personal Information that may be Collected Includes:_

  * Personal Information such as Full Name, Address, Date of Birth, ID Number and Occupation.
  * Financial Information such as assets, investment experience and monthly income, in order to evaluate your trading experience
  * When funding your account or withdrawing from your account, we may request documents such as a copy of an ID document, utility bills and a bank statements.

The above information collected from clients, helps Company understand your financial needs, provide you with products and services suitable to your needs, process your account transactions in a timely manner as well as provide you with the highest level of customer support.  
No personal information will be shared with any third parties without the customer’s permission or by an order of a competent authority.

 _How is information collected from Company's Clients:_

  * On Completion of Electronic registration forms placed on the Website or Minisite(s).
  * When funding or withdrawing from trading accounts.
  * When trading on the platform.
  * When contacting the Company or responding to a promotion advertised.

There is certain information that is indirectly collected by Company such as: IP Address, operating system, software configuration and the use of cookies.

 _What is the use of information collected_

  * To verify clients identity.
  * To set up, maintain and manage clients' trading account.
  * To process deposits and withdraws in clients' trading account.
  * To keep clients up to date with news, updates and new promotions.
  * To analyze client's activity in order to improve and provide clients with the best products and services.
  * To provide clients with top quality customer support.

 _The Sharing of Clients Personal Information:_

  * In order to open, operate and service your personal trading account, Company may share information with service providers such as attorneys, accountants, auditors, and other financial professionals
  * In order to protect against fraud, money laundering, unauthorized transactions, claims or other liabilities, or by instruction of an applicable authority.
  * With affiliates and introducing brokers, mainly for the calculation of these entity's compensation.

 _How Does The Company Protect The Information You Provide:_

  * The Company uses the data security technology, firewalls and data encryption software.
  * Every client owns his own personal user name and password which he uses to access The Company's platform.
  * Access to client information is restricted to a small group of management and employees that need to use this information

 _Links found on the Website:_

Links to external sites may be found on the website. The Company takes no responsibility for the content on the external websites and advice to all clients to read the privacy policy of the external websites before leaving any personal information.

 _Deposits and Withdrawals:_

Deposits - Currently, the Minimum deposit amount is USD500. There is no limit on the maximum amount that can be deposited.  
Withdrawals - There is no Minimum or Maximum limits on withdrawals requests.The above Min/Max limits may be changed by the Company at any time.

 _Credit Cards Policy:_

The Company does not store full cardholder data in electronic format and does not process or transmit any cardholder data on their systems or premises.

 _Questions, Concerns or Complaints:_

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints, please don't hesitate to contact us via phone, email or chat.
